A secret is not safe if the truth has a witness.
Irresistible is a drama, mystery, thriller film directed by Ann Turner.
A wife and mother is consumed by the thought that her husband's
co-worker is trying to win him away from her and their family.
Sophie Hartley, played by Susan Sarandon.
Craig, played by Sam Neill.
Mara, played by Emily Blunt.
Sam, played by Charles Tingwell.
Jimmy, played by William McInnes.
Jen, played by Georgie Parker.
Irresistible is a 2006 Australian mystery drama film written and directed by Ann
Turner and starring Susan Sarandon, Sam Neill, and Emily Blunt.
Sophie is an American book illustrator and her family is
disrupted by her husband's new co-worker, Mara.
Sophie is made to look crazy by the activities of Mara.
The film explores themes of infidelity, obsession, paranoia, seduction, stalker.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.